[
  {
    "level": "2",
    "question": "MOV R1, 5",
    "options": ["19400005", "1901", "01400005"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "2",
    "question": "SUB R1, R2",
    "options": ["03400001", "13400007", "0301"],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "2",
    "question": "MOV R1, R4",
    "options": ["1903", "1901", "194000016"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "2",
    "question": "CMP ACC, R4",
    "options": ["270003", "1901", "1323"],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "2",
    "question": "ADD R1, 16",
    "options": ["19400010", "0108", "014000010"],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "2",
    "question": "WRT",
    "options": ["97", "1901", "01400005"],
    "correctOption": 1,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "2",
    "question": "RD",
    "options": ["19400005", "87", "195800016"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "2",
    "question": "BRI LOOP",
    "options": ["19400003", "1901", "310003"],
    "correctOption": 3,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "2",
    "question": "RDS ADR",
    "options": ["19500000", "390000", "05480000"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  },
  {
    "level": "2",
    "question": "DIV R4, 16",
    "options": ["05480010", "07580010", "19500010"],
    "correctOption": 2,
    "points": 10
  }
]
